

APTITUDES

- Able to think about hing-quality solutions to specific problems and resolve them with technological tools and software.
- Autodidact and fast learner, able to adapt to different work flows and practices.
- Team worker with hing comunaction abilities to cooperate with cooworkers.

LET'S TALK

(+58) 414-6416513 contact@jhosephweb.dev https://www.linkedin.com/in/jhosephweb/

TAKE A LOOK TO MY PORTFOLIO

www.jhosephweb.dev

Jhoseph Guerrero

Fullstack developer | Software Engineer

THIS IS MY STORY:

I'm a professional fullstack web developer who loves what he does, an enthusiast for learning new things and get more experience everyday. i like to cooperate with my team and create a friendly atmosphere and make the working journey feel like something to look forward to.

EXPERIENCE

DEVSKTOP

CO-FOUNDER
MAR 2019 - PRESENT

- Build and design multiple websites and web apps.
- Payment managment software for "Fe y alegria" schools.
- Medical appointment managment app.
- Social media content creation.

REDXAM

WEB DEVELOPER & BACKEND LEAD AUG 2020 - PRESENT

- Build backend infrastructure and bussiness logic.
- Configure servers.
- Set continous integration.
- Configure bitcoin node.
- Integrate KYC and bank payments API.

EDUCATION

URBE University

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (WITH HONORS) SEPT 2017- MAR 2021

certified to build high-quality web, mobile, and desktop applications that meet the requirements of a business and empower the end user.

CEVAZ

ENGLISH LANGUAGE PROGRAM

Certified to speak, write, listen, read and hold conversations in advance english .

LANGUAGES AND TOOLS

